I've been literally on stage workshopping my show,
What Would the Ancestors Say?
for a year off the top of my head.
I sometimes feel like in our history books,
it goes like slavery and then Martin Luther King.
I think about Clarence Thomas like all the time.
Our ancestors were not fighting and dying
and escaping to be white.
Blah, blah, blah, pop, pop.
You know, some of all the same great to be free.
Sure, I have bullet points,
but ultimately it hasn't been on the page.
Now it's time.
It's time to put the words to the page.
It's time to publish the work
and it's time to memorialize it.
However, in the process of doing so,
I've uncovered so much and I've expounded the facts,
the jokes, the commentary in so many dope, intricate ways
that I want to actually do a read through of the script
as it is on the page.
And I want you guys to be there
to experience this evolution of process.
We also have a Q and A scheduled for after.
So for my next free show at my residency
at the People's Forum in New York City,
happening on September 6th at 6 p.m.,
you will get to be a part of an intimate,
exclusive read through of What Would The Ancestors Say?
in its latest iteration before publication.
This is a free show unless you want to save your seat,
in which case it's a $10 donation to the TPF.
Otherwise, make sure you show up at five
because it's first come, first serve.
Also, you can join on live stream.
Come be a part of the process with me, y'all,
and Harriet and Frederick and Checkahoe and Dolly
and everybody who is a part of What Would The Ancestors Say?